<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Home</title>
    <link>https://jkkronk.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jkkronk.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SVGD Toy example</title>
      <link>https://jkkronk.github.io/2021/svgd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkkronk.github.io/2021/svgd/</guid>
      <description>Toy example: Stein Variational Gradient Descent: A General Purpose Bayesian Inference Algorithm Intro Stein Variational Gradient Descent (SVGD) is a variational inference algorithm that by solving a deterministic optimisation problem seek to create a set of samples from an untraceable posterior distribution. More specifically SVGD tries to transform a set of initial random particles to match the posterior distribution.
You can read more in the original paper: https://arxiv.org/abs/1608.04471
I coded a toy example to understand SVGD deeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated MRI papers</title>
      <link>https://jkkronk.github.io/2021/080621/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkkronk.github.io/2021/080621/</guid>
      <description>Awesome Accelerated-MRI-Reconstruction-Papers Hey, I came across awesome git repos listing ml papers on different topics. Here are two examples: link and link. Other people also find these curated lists awesome since there is a couple of hundreds of forks and thousands of stars. Since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any on Accelerated MRI reconstruction, I took the time and created my own curated list. Enjoy it here
Cheers, Jonatan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISMRM 2021 Highlight</title>
      <link>https://jkkronk.github.io/2021/ismrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkkronk.github.io/2021/ismrm/</guid>
      <description>ISMRM 2021 Highlights How to translate ML into the clinic - Shreyas Vasanawala On the first day of the conference, Vasanawala from Stanford gave a brilliant talk about integrating ml in all steps of the medical imaging pipeline, from scheduling through reconstruction to image processing. He first stated that ml is not typically used in clinical practice but then gave many examples of integrating it in practice. One example of exciting work he mentioned was “One-Click Spine MRI”, where HeartVista shows an automatic process for spine MRI scan prescription.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
